(Heart Pairing)
Going beyond simple flirting,
now, we show you young people
who want to date...
someone they want to marry.
After eight years, after "Heart Signal,"
Channel A presents...
the best-ever dating reality show.
Welcome to Heart Pairing.
(Heart Pairing starts now.)
(Boosting dopamine)
The atmosphere is heated up.
I have nine years of experience
in "Heart Signal."
I've been married for 20 years.
I'm the right person
for hosting Heart Pairing.
I'm Yoon Jong Shin.
You're just right for this.
And here's someone
who rarely appears in variety shows.
Actress Lee Chung Ah joined us
in hosting the show.
Hello, I'm Actress Lee Chung Ah.
The only dating show I watched
was "Heart Signal 4."
It really was...
- more dramatic than a drama.
- Right.
Hearing that the crew was creating
a new dating reality show,
I came here feeling excited,
- and it already makes my heart flutter.
- Right?
My heart flutters so much.
Actually for me, "Heart Signal" was...
the first and the last dating show
I watched.
You should have appeared
in the show, Si Won.
- That's right.
- Watching it now,
I feel I should have been there.
The mood there is so nice.
I also had an experience with this show.
Although my gut feeling isn't good,
watching them makes me feel...
that they're around my age.
(Mimi feels that the residents
are around her age.)
Today, as a friend,
I will try to represent their position.
Mimi, you're the best age to marry, right?
I want to deny it,
but that's right.
I will do my best...
to look for someone.
And here's someone
who sent us a love call...
saying she wants to be in this show.
Dreams come true.
I watch all the dating shows,
but "Heart Signal" is the way to go.
- That's right.
- In my heart,
"Heart Signal" is a story that isn't over.
It's a show I really love.
So, joining in Heart Pairing...
makes me so happy.
Then...
can you predict who will be a couple
in the last episode?
I think I can guess it right.
- Watching only the first episode?
- I'll give it a try.
In the previous "Heart Signal,"
from flirting to dating,
young love of people in their 20s
was described.
This time, for one month,
the show describes the process
of looking for a partner...
the residents want to get married.
Dating and marriage are different...
in the mindset.
Are they quite different
from the beginning?
They surely are.
They have different weights.
I have a dim memory about it, though.
(I can't remember exactly.)
Now, from the beginning stage
of a relationship,
I get to think about a lot of things.
You can't just date someone
only because you're attracted.
If you marry just because
you're attracted...
You're dragged.
- You're dragged?
- For whole life.
I understand.
- It seems they went somewhere.
- With a passport.
There's a rumor they went to Europe.
Of Europe, they went
to the city of romance,
Tuscany.
In Italy.
They're in big trouble.
Something's going to happen.
I can't believe I'm its first viewer.
I'm excited.
(What kind of person
do you want to marry?)
(Someone who puts effort...)
(into work and family)
I'm already immersed.
(I want to spend time together.)
(How do you want to sleep
after getting married?)
(What's the monthly income
you expect as a couple?)
(- How will you do the housework?
- Do you want to have children?)
Now that they talk about marriage,
it feels totally different.
(33 questions on marriage)
(One person's thoughts...)
I got goosebumps. What's that?
(are made into a book.)
(Is there someone you like?
Then pick the book she wrote.)